Richard J. Reliford, II

Tucson, AZ 85745 • (818) 934-6769 • rjreliford2@gmail.com

QUALIFICATIONS SUMMARY

Goal-oriented and highly dependable college student dedicated to pursuing opportunities in information technology while simultaneously exemplifying a commitment to the community and enthusiasm to engage with others.

- Technical Skills: HTML/CSS, Java/JavaScript, Python, Game Design, Web Design, Microsoft Office
- **Key Strengths:** Loyal team member, inventive, multi-tasker, experienced with problem-solving and handling conflict.
- Adult and Pediatric First Ald/CPR/AED Certified

EDUCATION

B.S., Information Sciences & Technology, minor in Game Design (Anticipated May 2023)

Game Design and Development Certificate (Anticipated May 2023)

University of Arizona, Tucson, AZ

Awards/Recognition: Hall Council President, NRHH (National Residence Hall Honorary) Rising Diamond Award; NRHH Distinguished Service Award; HLC (Hall Leadership Conference) 2019 Spotlight Award; Bronze Pin Award; Top Ten Program IACURH (Intermountain Affiliate of College and University Residence Halls) Camp Wildcat the Hero Theseus Award

EXPERIENCE HIGHLIGHTS

UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA, Tucson, AZ

Student, Information Sciences & Technology, minor in Game Design and Development (2019 - Present)

Currently pursuing a comprehensive four-year course of study in demanding information sciences and technology program in anticipation of a future career in computer science.

- IT Student Assistant for U of A Athletics o Providing assistance with supporting the coaches, staff, and athletes with any technical concerns and issues.
 - o Updating, changing and maintaining technological devices for U of A.
- Relevant Coursework: CSC 110 Introduction to Python, PAH 150A1 Video Game Sights, Sounds, and Stories, GAME 310, ISTA 131
- Volunteer Opportunities: Tucson High YL Leader, Campus Pantry Volunteer, University of Arizona Conference Rep/Spirit Leader, Camp Wildcat Camp Director/Counselor, Camp Wildcat Co-Fundraising Chair
- Was selected as **Director of Recognition** tasked with ensuring the welfare of 50+ student residents.
- · Created the new Camp Wildcat website with a co-worker

Mission1Race, Culver City, CA

Web Designer/App Developer/Film Editor (Summer 2019 - May 2020)

Worked to develop a website that met the requirements given by the CEO using Wix. In charge of creating an app for the company. Provided a major role in the editing of the company's documentary.

The Nocturnal Operations Company, Los Angeles, CA

Web Designer/Film Assistant (Winter 2018 and Summer 2019)

Worked to enhance the company's website based on the CEO's suggestions. As a Film Assistant, I worked with the director, writer, and producer on casting the roles as well as making sure everything went smoothly on filming days.

Cinemark, Marina Del Rey, CA

Usher/Ticket Taker (Spring-Summer 2019)

Demonstrated customer service skills by engaging guests, addressing complaints/concerns, ensuring the safety of guests, and directing guests to theaters.

UofA, Tucson, AZ

Campus Pantry Director (May 2021- Present)

Overseeing the campus pantry at the University of Arizona, conducting meetings with staff, partners, and donators.

UofA, Tucson, AZ

Campus Pantry Operations/Distribution Assistant (May 2020 - May 2021)

Helps out with various aspects of the pantry during distribution as well as organizing and helping out during food drives as well.

UofA, Tucson, AZ

Lead Camp Counselor (June 2021 - July 2021)

In charge of all the counselors and campers that came to this camp. Helped maintain order and consistency with quality counseling of the camp.

UofA, Tucson, AZ

Camp Counselor (May 2021 - August 2021)

In charge of providing a fun safe environment for the campers. Attending to their needs whenever asked.